Guide to the John Taber papers, 1880-1965.
Taber, John papers
- Assorted Files, 1931-1957
  - Post War, Date Unknown (Box 127)
  - Post War Economic Policy and Planning, Date Unknown (Box 127)
  - Post War Relief, Date Unknown (Box 135)
  - Public Iaws, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Public Lands, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Public Lands, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Public works, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Public Works, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Soldier Vote, Date Unknown (Box 127)
  - State Department, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - State Department, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - State, Justice, Judiciary and Related Agencies, Date Unknown (Box 165)
  - Subsidy - Milk, Date Unknown (Box 127)
  - Supplementals, Date Unknown (Box 165)
  - T.V.A. Appropriations, Date Unknown (Box 165)
  - Townsend Plan, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Treasury - Post Office Departments, Date Unknown (Box 165)
  - U.N.R.R.A., Date Unknown (Box 135)
  - Unamerican Activities, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Unamerican Activities, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Unarranged, Date Unknown (Box 80)
  - Unarranged, Date Unknown (Box 81)
  - Urgent Deficiency, Date Unknown (Box 165)
  - Veterans' Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Veterans' Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Veterans Affairs A - O, Date Unknown (Box 180)
  - Veterans Affairs P - Z and misc., Date Unknown (Box 181)
  - Voice of America, Date Unknown (Box 135)
  - Ways and Means, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Wrapped Up Agriculture Department Publications (Box 131)
  - Yugoslavia, Date Unknown (Box 135)